Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hi. my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me. but I have something
to tell you that's going to sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're going
to believe me because
you're very good at
telling when I'm lying.
Evie. can you check the calibration of my
targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed into me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey Evie. take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was going to happen.
And the only way to stop it was to make
everyone forget me.
First in and like two. let's go.
Oh my gosh. we're here.
We made it.
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest you've
ever been in your entire life right now.
I can't.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
I'm really. really understanding the
culture out here in Boston.
It's just so different.
And sometimes Spider-Man
has to do the hard
thing. even if it breaks
Peter Parker's heart.
And maybe that's my responsibility.
To live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope that deep down something inside
of you remembers that you love me too.
But until then. I'm just going to be
Spider-Man.
Incoming!
Members of the Man Freddy crime syndicate
were apprehended by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey. you live on the same floor.
Oh. cool.
Doesn't anybody ever come up here?
Not unless they like us best of us.
We've just been using it for storage.
That's perfect.
Hey. everyone.
Sophomore year and that is back.
Older. wiser. flyer.
Let's go.
Whoa.
What?
What is on your face?
How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look like an assistant coach.
Huh.
You sure you want to do this. Scorpion?
Did you miss me. Spidey?
If I drop you for me. how long do you
think it would take you to hit the ground?
Well. I don't know.
You tell me.
Let's end this on a high note.
huh?
Yo. Lonnie.
What happened?
The wolf.
All the evidence you're gonna need is in
the trunk of his car.
You trying to take my job. Spider-Man?
Hey. you guys are the professionals.
I'm just the volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man. crime rates have
dropped to a record low.
Police and damage control give much of the
credit to the masked hero.
Initiate HUD test.
Armed robbery at Civic Union Bank.
In the past six months. he has taken down
every major crime lord across the five
boroughs. including the super-powered
ninja group The Hand.
He is the pride of New
York City. the hero every
grown-up relies on and
every kid wants to be.
Final semester at MIT.
Oh my gosh. we're graduating in a month.
We've made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night swimming in the Charles River with
Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food fight at the banana
lounge.
Pulling all-nighters in stud five with MJ
and Nate Doll.
It feels like yesterday I was sitting on a
roof with MJ dreaming about coming here
together and I still can't believe we did
it.
I'm so grateful for all the friends that
I've made.
I couldn't imagine going through this with
anyone else.
Dad. who do you think is actually watching
these?
Uh. I don't know. but maybe someone.
Okay. bye someone.
What?
We're done.
No!
I mean. we're talking about downtown
Brooklyn in broad daylight.
High-profile job like that.
You know that Fazza was involved.
Yeah. I hear you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. I'm going through his financial records
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying. you do something you
love. you don't work a day in your life.
Okay. me as that.
Mom. where's my calculator?
I don't know.
Trust me. all right?
Being married to the job never ends well.
Well. don't worry about it.
I'll be okay.
Oh. yeah?
You still getting them headaches.
though?
Uh. yeah. but um. but I'll be fine.
Mm-hmm. I don't know. man.
I think your body's trying to tell you
something.
Like you need to get out of that suit
every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know. puppy.
What you need is some real human
connection.
Oh. what?
And we're not connecting?
Nah. dude.
I don't know your name. your face.
or nothing about you.
I don't think you've ever asked me a
question about my life.
Sure I have.
Yeah. what are my kids' names?
Uh. well. for starters. your son's name's
Poppy.
Is it Spiderman?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spiderman.
Gosh.
A hijacked tank is heading southbound past
34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work. lucky you.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
I got you. Spidey!
No. no. I don't need you.
You okay. kid?
Yeah. you're okay.
See you later.
You wouldn't know it just
by looking at it. but this very
street was completely destroyed
in the Battle of New Orleans.
Come on. come on!
What
the hell. Frank?
You just hit me with the fan!
Quit your whimprint.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You're goddamn right we're not.
This time you're gonna get the hell out of
my way.
Well. you mean instead of saving your
life?
You gotta talk about that Staten Island
bullshit again.
Now. well. you said it. not me.
Look. man. you can't just shoot yourself
out of every situation.
Innocent people get hurt.
What do you think's downrange of that
tank. dumb dog?
Shoot yourself.
Jackass.
This frickin' guy.
I'm gonna kill this kid.
DeWolf. you gonna stop that thing or what?
It's heading straight for the Damage
Control Detention Center.
I'm trying.
Try harder. there's a lot of scary dudes
locked up in there.
Well. who do you think put them in there?
Let's go. Scorpion.
Moving day.
It's
armed and dangerous.
Get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spiderman?
Where am I?
What the... Keep
perfect questioning.
Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride. Scorpion.
You won't be seeing my stay light in
Supermax.
Scorpions are nocturnal. buddy.
The building is under attack.
Get the prisoner out of here. now.
You gotta take off now.
The building has been breached.
Go. go.
Change of plans.
Take him to the helipad at Bellevue.
That's an order from direct to Mexico.
Go. now.
Copy that.
How did I get up here?
Spiderman.
Save me. would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
You know. the whole time
you've been chasing me. you
forgot to ask yourself a
very important question.
What's in the tank?
Spiderman?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Okay. good job.
You guys okay?
You good?
I swear. all the things I said I did.
I don't remember doing anything.
It's okay. it's okay.
Look. let these people take a carry.
I would never hurt you.
Okay.
I love you. Spiderman.
Yeah. all right. buddy. all right.
Hey. what do you got?
Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue.
10 minutes later. a guard walked him right
out the door.
What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from the damage control warehouse
in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor who worked there.
You got a motive?
Nah. nah.
And no criminal record.
Scorpion must have gotten to her somehow.
Oh. okay.
Yeah. maybe.
What do you mean. maybe?
I mean. I don't know.
But I know someone to Mike.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi. uh. is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
Okay.
I think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
Uh. what?
You don't wear clothes in the manual.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your tech said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine. thanks.
I'll just... My
office. my rules.
This way you get to
enjoy a nice relaxing soak
and I get to see that you
don't have any weapons.
And we both win.
Okay.
Really?
But you never take that off?
No. you know. it defeats the whole
anonymous thing.
Even for your girlfriend or boyfriend?
Or whatever.
There's a lot of conjecture among them.
And super graphic artwork.
Have you seen the one with you and the ten
mysterious?
Wait. I've seen it.
It's hard to unsee. to be honest.
But look. I don't have any one.
I just kind of keep to myself.
All by yourself all the time?
No wonder you're so sad.
I'm not so sad.
A little bit.
Could we just talk
about what I came here to
talk to you about the
attack on damage control?
Yes. so that is more your area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers are focusing on
big potato stuff.
Right. okay.
Well. there's more to it than that.
You know. the driver and the others who
were helping.
It was like someone was talking to me
through them.
Like someone was looking at me through
their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control.
Exactly.
Like how they used on me in the red room.
And the other weirdos.
Right. right.
No. I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably more like
possession.
Possession?
Like a ghost. or a demon. or in Russia we
have Leshy.
Leshy rules the forest and can possess...
Sorry.
Whatever it is. they are looking for
something.
This is the fourth attack on the damage
control facility this month.
What do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today.
there was a cross-agency
cyber security alert
that got triggered.
Someone accessed the
damage control restricted servers.
using credentials from 30
employees from the waystation.
They all searched for the same thing.
VMAX.
VMAX?
Well. what does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tech. or secretive
weapon programs. or launch codes. or.
..
I don't know.
This is for you to figure out.
This is small baby potato stuff.
not big potato brain stuff.
Okay. okay.
Maybe I'll just go ask damage control
myself.
You know. you're not completely anonymous
anymore.
I have seen your belly button.
Okay.
Bye.
Hi. I got an appointment
with... Director Metzger. yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA.
Arachnid.
Please remove your face covering for
identity scan.
Oh. no. I can't do that.
That's not possible.
To remove your face covering will result
in defensive measures.
Defensive measures?
Guys. guys. guys. I can't take my mask
off.
I'm smart.
Spider-Man.
He's all right.
At ease.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger. director of damage control.
How are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We had to beef up security around here.
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No. not at all.
All right. come on this way.
This floor is mostly research and
administrative.
Downstairs. we have incident cleanup.
Agent training.
Hey. what are they doing here?
It's okay.
The hand works for us now.
After you brought
them in. I realized that.
fundamentally. they're a
group of kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly. all the things
that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable
part of our security team.
You can look at the many threats that face
us and see only danger.
Or you can see opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of Shockler. these are a
nuisance.
But it doesn't mean we can't learn from
the technology or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive
energy into something.
Useful.
That's the true meaning of damage control.
Be careful with that.
Right this way.
I wanted to talk to you about the recent
attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please. have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with a threat we
can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolf's report.
I believe you understand exactly what
we're up against.
Someone or something that can hop into
people's minds.
But not yours.
No. I mean it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get
in here and find whatever it
is looking for. the consequences
could be unimaginable.
Well. let me guess.
Is whatever it's looking for in that giant
vault?
There are some things because of the
nature of my job I cannot tell you.
But I believe you are our best defense
against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech. Director.
I'll do everything that I can.
I promise.
Well. then consider yourself a friend of
damage control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Oh. I wanted to ask.
The phrase VMAX doesn't mean anything to
you. does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh. it's just. you know.
nature of being a superhero.
there are some things
I just can't tell you.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great.
Keep it up.
I don't think Metzger
knows any more than we do.
but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
You want to help?
The best thing you could do is find
Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah. I know.
I have every camera in the city running
official recognition scam porn.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably for the best.
But look. if he shows his face.
we'll know.
Do you have any. any thanks?
Done at the end.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Uh-huh.
Easy.
Hey. uh. also. you got any sharp fire
energy?
Yeah.
Oh. no. no. no.
I don't want any.
That stuff will kill you.
You know. all my
friends were drinking them
during the finals. and
now they're addicted.
So I'm gonna need you to not sell me any.
Memorize my face.
Please. do not sell this guy any sharp
fire.
Sure.
Whatever.
Actually. I'll take one.
Last one.
Maybe two?
And then never sell me any.
Damn it.
Okay. you like this one.
Oh. thank you.
You need a drink.
Take this.
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh. um. see. you've stumbled across my
board.
I'm not one of those weirdos. I swear.
He actually saved me and my friends' lives
a few times in high school.
Oh. cool.
Yeah. yeah.
And ever since. I've just been trying to
figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the
world or anything. just to... No.
You know. and to hopefully thank him face
to face.
I actually created this app that monitors
his sightings.
Well. you created Spidey Tracker?
You heard of it.
Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
Little chat room right there.
Now. we know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down to
two prime suspects.
Yeah. if you knew who they were.
it would really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
Oh. I'm. um... God. there's
like 50 people in an apartment.
Statistically speaking. that means at
least two of them are sociopaths.
Which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
Oh. they're. uh. housewarming gift.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh. okay.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
It's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm. uh... I'm. uh... I'm. uh...
I'm. uh... I'm a... I'm a nerd.
I'm a nerd.
Oh. you two don't know each other?
I'm a... I'm a... I'm
a... I'm a neighbor.
I'm a... I'm a neighbor.
I'm a... I'm a...
I'm a neighbor.
I'm gonna go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you. main nerd.
Nerd.
Main nerd.
Yeah.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yeah. no. I went.
And?
And I got the job.
Oh my god. MJ. that's amazing!
I turned it down.
What?
Yeah. I don't want to work for some
soulless corporation.
They're not all soulless.
Okay. they're all mostly soulless.
But don't you want. like. health
insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. but at what cost?
Depends on your deductible.
Oh. you mean like your principles?
Yes.
Sorry.
I don't know. I know it sounds cheesy.
but...
Something is just telling me that I'm
supposed to be waiting for something.
Great. you know?
Okay. um. to. uh...
Waiting for something great?
Waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
Oh!
Your new home.
Dude. this is top shelf.
Just like you.
I want to hide this.
I lifted this off and then again.
But what if Ned needs the fire of a
thousand sharks?
You mean heart palpitations.
You can't save everyone.
I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
When we get into MIT. we should live
together.
Yeah. for sure.
Yeah. I love that.
Be a fresh start.
And we'll all be together.
Yeah. no. you're right. Ned.
Fresh start.
You're gonna forget who I am.
Okay. who are you?
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm gonna come and find you.
And I'll explain everything.
And I'll always wait.
Wait and tell me. won't you see me again?
My name is Peter Parker. and I like a
coffee.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
now that I've got power?
You know. this whole thing can get really
scary.
You know that?
Well. yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah. and things can
change. like very quickly.
ways that we can't
even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
Oh. I. uh. I live here.
I just. um. I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that my shirt?
No.
Oh. keep the haw-Oh. shh.
Hi. Peter.
You have 107 new alerts.
Please check backlog.
What is happening?
The results of your body
scan show a surge in
the hormones associated
with your arachnid DNA.
Resulting in the formation of organic web
spinnerets and dangerously heightened
sensory receptors.
Okay. but I feel fine.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced any recent traumatic
events?
Peter?
I'm fine. Evie.
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take some time to
rebalance.
Well. that's not really an option.
is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
Alert.
Senses are overloaded.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking in too
much information at once.
Okay.
It's okay.
Alright. organic webs.
Peter too had them.
He was cool.
You're cool.
Oh my God. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs.
Come on. and webs!
What's going on. Evie?
Shots fired at the Damage Control Data
Center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Come on. three. two... Webstock!
Webstock!
Bird bird!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Webstock!
Oh God!
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for V-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
Scorpion. do we really gotta keep doing
this?
My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
Webstock!
What's happening to you?
You can't sense me anymore.
You.
What's going on with you. Spider-Man?
Warning.
Arachnid hormones increasing.
We need some help over here.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
Oh my God.
The wolf. is she hurt?
Is she okay?
No.
Just let me go.
What is going on over here?
That wasn't Scorpion. okay?
I mean. it was. but he was possessed by
whatever.
Hijacked that tank. okay?
Look. please. can
I just... Slow down.
Listen. I don't know what this is.
but I need you to pull that together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know. I'm sorry.
If you act like this again. I cannot
protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
Through lattice chromodynamics.
we can arrange time and space in a grid.
which allows us to simulate the quarks
binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this a question about protons or
more stuff about Avengers?
Guys. I love to tell
stories. but you know. I got
to teach you some
physics at some point. yeah.
All right.
Let it rip. Cindy.
If Banos was so worried
about overpopulation. why
didn't he just use the magic
glove to make more food?
Arthur. you want to answer that question?
Hulk!
No!
Excuse me. Dr. Banner?
I. um... You okay?
Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to you about your
inhibitor.
Oh. sure.
Don't worry.
It's got fail-safes.
I'm not going to turn into the big. green.
raging monster machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me let this thing off.
run.
No!
No. but you're using target-specific short
end-affearing RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing. you're just
incorporating the gamma radiation.
What'd you say your name was?
Uh. Ned.
Leeds.
So you found a way to suppress the
expression of DNA. even as it's undergoing
the mutation due to gamma radiation.
right?
Yes.
Okay. so my question is.
would that same thing be
possible with DNA that's
mutating for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is mixed
with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically. yes. it's possible.
Yes.
So could you suppress only some parts of
that DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects. but just keep all
the good stuff?
You mean. like if I wanted to keep some
parts of Halk but not others?
Right.
It would be enormously
dangerous and complex. but if you
were able to target the
correct mRNA strand. possibly.
Wait. so you could just turn the mutating
gene on and off as long as you do it
before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same thinking.
you could even develop some kind of
automatic inhibitor that would just adjust
to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking
about a universal inhibitor
that would control anyone
who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Well. yeah. but it's theoretical.
right?
You're not one of my students.
are you?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've taken enough of your time.
I gotta get some books back to the
library.
The library's that way.
Right.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Well. what parts of nature are good or
bad?
What if you're trying to
control the expression
of something that
needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
Okay. come on.
Upload inhibitor beta bill seven.
Uploaded.
Would you like to run a test?
Yeah. run it.
Spiders have three stages in their life
cycle.
Each stage is characterized by physical
changes. with the largest changes
occurring during the beautiful transition
to adulthood.
For those who make it through.
molting amounts to a kind of beeper...
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Turning off video.
Inhibitor active.
Come on. come on.
Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid hormones to your
baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. Evie.
Let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert.
Inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah. I'm sensing that.
Alert.
Senses are overloaded.
Overload.
Web grenades activated.
Oh. shit.
Inhibitor field test one.
Failure.
Yo. Spider-Man.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm just trying out some new tech.
Oh. yeah.
To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me. huh?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only person I've met
that I can't... hop into.
I'm sure that's really
frustrating for you.
Well. I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
I don't know why a half-human.
half-Spider would decide to work for an
organization whose strong mission is to
hunt down anybody who's different.
Damage control isn't after you because
you're different.
They're hunting you down because you're
dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple Spider.
let me spell it out for you.
Damage control has something that I need.
Oh. you mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
Oh. you sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment is
kind of like a parody of where
you think a sad single guy
in his twenties might live.
Takeout containers. free weights.
protein powder?
You're bluffing.
You know. you're not hard to track down.
Peter.
Well. at least not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing.
though.
And of all places...
Coffee cup.
AV Display homework station.
You spent four years erasing Peter Parker
from existence?
No wonder the Spider's trying to swallow
up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
No.
Her roommate was nice enough to post a new
address online.
How about this?
I'll race you there.
If you touch her...
Better start swinging.
I'm fast.
Hey!
It's a long way to MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
Evie. track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies between
subjects.
Please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
In a race for the love of his life.
then it's not looking good.
Come on. Spidey.
Keep up.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Evie. run these numbers with the others.
Analyzing jump distances for patterns.
Get me that jump data!
Calculating.
Come on. I need an answer!
Calculations complete.
You have a limit to your jump radius.
don't you?
Thirty-three feet.
I don't see anybody up here for you to hop
into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting near her.
Hey. hey. hey. hey!
I'm sorry. but you're in the wrong place.
You're in danger.
Where's your roommate?
What?
Where's Nick?
I bossed it with friends.
Why?
Okay. good.
You got a couple of things.
What?
I don't know if you're the real Spider-Man
or not coming with you.
We don't have time for this.
Please. come on.
You need to get out of my apartment.
Look. this is going to
sound insane. but there is
someone who is after you
who is really dangerous. okay?
And I promised you that I would keep you
safe.
Please. you just have to trust me.
Come on.
Fine.
Where would you stop?
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay. we should be safe up here.
SUBS: CRETA STAR
Okay. we'll see from what?
Uh. I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
I don't know.
You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
Um. I wish I could tell you.
I just...
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years.
all the times that Spider-Man saved.
either me or Ned.
It was the Washington
Monument. and then it
was London. and Prague.
and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice is a coincidence.
but over and over again.
We knew each other.
Tell me I'm wrong.
You're wrong.
What were we?
Were we classmates. or friends.
or something?
Look. I don't know what you're talking
about.
Were we something more?
I just... I can't... I can't remember.
And I feel like someone scrambled my brain.
and you're the only one who would know why.
This is crazy. and I can't... I
know that you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of me that still
remembers.
I hate the other.
Oh. this is too much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead. Peter.
Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to for so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell.
and reunites to serve cross-lovers.
I'm David Vollman.
You really are a simple spider.
aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's. uh... She's smart.
A little dark and twisted.
I mean. it is sad.
There is. like. no thoughts of you in
here.
Whatsoever.
But you knew that. didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone the
way that I love her. then you'd
know that what you're doing
right now is unforgivable.
Oh. is that so?
You know. some people would kill to hold
the person they loved one last time.
Stop it now.
Oof.
You're running out of time. Peter.
Soon enough. it won't just be your friends
who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should write a letter to
yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
Oh!
M.J.
No. no. no.
Oh. God.
Oh. God. please. no. come on.
Come on. come on. come
on.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Stop.
Wait. wait. stop. stop. please.
I'll quit.
You win. you win. you win.
Just don't hurt her.
You're a mess. Spider-Man.
Any time I want.
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect M.J.
Even from herself.
It really is a nice letter.
A little heavy-handed.
I'm not bad.
You're okay.
I'm gonna take you someplace safe.
Take me to 3165.
Lafayette Street.
Navigating to Empire State University.
I got you. I got you.
You sure?
Yep.
Okay. because I feel like I'm slipping a
little bit.
You're not slipping.
Okay.
You're okay. you're okay. you're okay.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay. can we just slow down for like two
seconds. please?
We're almost there.
Yeah. yeah. but you just told me I was
mind-controlled.
Well. not technically.
And you're lucky I believe in that stuff.
okay?
Because governments have been doing it for
years. especially the French.
Are you okay?
Yeah. look. sorry. I'm just trying to take
you someplace safe. okay?
Go. go. go. safe.
Oh. watch out!
You're losing it. kid.
Thought you'd be able to see that coming a
mile away.
What is wrong with you?
You could have killed us.
Excuse me?
You show up to my house unannounced.
what do you think's gonna happen?
Wait. this is your house?
No. don't.
Who the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
She's. um. you know.
No. I don't know.
That's why I just asked you.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
Yeah. looks like it.
Well. come on. you owe me.
Ah. for Christ's sake.
What's your sickest story?
Staten Island.
Nah. Staten Island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid.
Well. I gotta save it twice to get a favor
out of you.
That guy could hit me with a handful of
rice.
What does that sound like to you?
I had an exact amount of sugar on one of
them.
I see them right there.
I know exactly what I'm talking to you.
Okay. fine. go ahead.
What would you call that?
What does that sound like to you?
I don't care. I just wanna go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks. go home.
No. no. wait. wait. wait. wait.
wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
Please.
Hey. I've got to keep her safe.
okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right. just watch out for the
claymores.
I won't pick up pieces at you for the next
two weeks.
Hey. I definitely would not eat that
chili.
So you're telling me
that maniac behind all that
tank nonsense is nothing
but a goddamn teenager.
And it's not just a tank. it's every
attack on damage control this past month.
How does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know. Frank.
Beat your ass all over the street like
that.
She did not beat my ass.
Is this your family?
You should get the hell away from that.
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything. you don't move
anything.
You sure as shit don't ask me any goddamn
questions about anything.
It's the three rules.
I see why you like her.
Go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
Of course you do.
So I managed to pull this image from my
HUD and run it through the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple months ago.
Nobody.
She was in and out of foster
care. psych hospitals. and
then eventually she ran
away and dropped off the grid.
It's hardly any information about
her that hasn't been scrubbed.
but she's classified as a
telepath. and now we have a name.
Jean Grey.
Yeah.
These are the damage control sites that
she hasn't hit yet.
So if she surfaces. then my facial
tracking program will pick her up.
Right.
Oh. yeah.
What then?
Well. don't worry about what then.
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it. huh?
I'm just supposed to sit here and babysit
your girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend. so... All
right. look. what's the plan. huh?
You just gotta hope that your facial
tracking program works. and you get
yourself killed. I gotta watch her the
rest of my life.
I'm not gonna get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just have to fix my inhibitor.
and then I'll be good to go.
What do you need to do that?
Frank. you do not have what I need to do
that. okay?
You've got some mouth on you.
What. do you think you have an anti-static
mat. a tonal probe. and micro-tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
Bombs.
Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe to maybe call
someone and let them know I'm okay?
Uh... like your boyfriend?
No. like my roommate.
Oh. um...
I don't think that's such a good idea.
you know?
Because she already knows who he is.
and she can inhabit anyone she wants.
so... Right. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. you're right.
Sorry.
No. it's fine.
I totally get it.
If I call my boyfriend. he'd just ask me a
bunch of questions that I couldn't answer.
and he'd tell me I was being withholding
again.
Withholding?
Yep.
Sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a
jerk.
Why do you think you're withholding?
I don't know.
He'd tell me mass vigilante behind the
curtain.
Um... okay. I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have. uh. Mrs. Spiderman?
Do I have Mrs. Spiderman?
Um... No.
No.
Why not?
Because. um...
I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
Really?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I. uh...
I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
I'm sorry. that must have been really hard
for you.
Yeah. it was. yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm okay.
You know what?
It's gonna come over.
Hold on. hold on. hold on. hold on.
hold on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
Um. it just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace. I was gonna
major in biochemical engineering. so...
Do you mind if I...
Oh. yeah. for sure.
Here.
There you go.
Wow.
So. does the device itself...
I mean. does it generate any kind
of radiation or... a magnetic field?
Because that would definitely interfere.
Oh. yeah. it has a micro-magnetic field.
but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
Oh. it actually dissipates into the
fabric. which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles.
Or whatever you call them.
Uh. they would create a field.
It would be tiny. but...
But it's on your head. which is very close
to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
Oh. MJ. that is genius.
Okay. this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. that feels better.
That feels totally better.
Oh. my head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
Oh. my God. MJ. that like totally worked.
You know. this is some really intense
stuff you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like. I mean.
this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the kind of stuff you put
on. like. I don't know. like a monster.
Well. if you see what's
been happening to me over
the last couple of days.
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with you for the last
few hours. and that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain.
A really good guy who might just be
changing.
Well. I don't mean to overstep.
I'll let you get back to it.
Can't sleep either. huh?
You want coffee?
Sure.
You get your shit fixed.
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean. it should
completely shut down her powers.
You know what else will work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
That has got to be the goofiest shit I've
ever seen in my life.
Well. you can't even take the mask off.
Drink a cup of coffee.
Don't take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she. kid?
I don't know.
That's horseshit.
Who is she?
I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
Who are you telling?
You care about her.
You're pretending not to lie.
I don't care about her.
Look. I don't know who she is.
Frank.
Hey. I don't have anybody.
I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me.
What do you know about me. kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this?
It's a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
If I had one second. people I love are
still breathing.
You think I'd be hiding behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to be something that
I'm not?
Acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match.
She's at the Damage Control HQ in
Manhattan.
I gotta go.
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Thanks. Frank.
Hey.
You're just gonna let him go by himself?
You know. I think he might need you.
Kinda like you needed him on Staten
Island.
You can't hide from me forever.
Bill.
You've got a strong door. but it's the
wall you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Grey.
And you know what I want.
Jean?
You looked me up.
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen to your girl
if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
And you're definitely not getting inside
that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know what you're dealing
with.
You know. you and Banner have a lot in
common.
Both fighting the losing battle against
the monster that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk you can't defend.
What the hell?
Oh. I see.
Trying to muzzle me like you muzzle
yourself?
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is. you're not getting it.
Like hell. I'm not.
Jean. don't do this.
Save your breath.
What
are you doing here?
You think I'm doing it.
I'm saving your ass.
This is way above your pay grade.
You better fight in the Hulk.
Really?
Stop shooting him.
You are your god damn mind.
Wait. Banner's not the problem.
She is.
I thought I told you to stay home and
watch MJ.
Yeah. you did.
And then she tells me I gotta come watch
you.
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing that for Dill?
Blushing?
God damn it.
I knew I should have brought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea.
Bring a bigger gun.
What are you gonna do?
Tickle in the death?
No. look. change your plan.
First we get this on the Hulk.
then we go after Jean.
I got one better.
That's the highest casualty producing
threat.
You contain it. I go find the source.
I take it down.
You got it?
Are you just trying to get out of fighting
the Hulk?
I guess so.
Okay. whatever. dude.
I got this.
Wait. don't prank. prank. prank.
prank.
What?
Do not kill her.
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
You know something?
I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna do it my way.
Just go.
Don't get within 33 feet.
So frustrating.
Hey.
Whoa.
This guy's got issues.
Oh. no.
No. not again.
Dr. Banner?
Is that you?
Spider-Man. what happened?
What am I?
Hey. hey. hey.
Did I do all this?
Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault.
She was in your mind.
She wasn't in control.
Look. here. here.
It's the only thing keeping the monster
inside.
It's okay.
I got another one.
I just need you to put this on.
What is it?
It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please. sir. there's people in the
building.
Just put it on.
You okay?
It's my head.
I think she broke something.
Is she still in there?
No.
It's the other guy.
Bruce?
Look. I can get you out of here.
okay?
I just need you to put that inhibitor on.
Get away from me!
He's coming.
I can't get you.
Yes. you can. Bruce.
Yes. you can!
Get out of the building!
Get out of the way of the heart of the
door!
Banner. please.
Look at me.
No banner.
No girl.
Call me Hulk.
I didn't know you could get that big.
Good luck with that. Peter.
There you are.
Just hold still!
No!
No lethal rounds.
Tracking time to detonation.
90 seconds to detonation.
I know. I know!
Why is your skin so thick?
Inhibitors cannot attack.
No. come on!
Please!
It's Peter.
I'm your friend.
Bruce!
Throw down your guns. or you'll get the
next one in the head.
Where is she?
What is she...
It's over. Jean.
Sarah... Send my gun.
Does anyone hurt?
Is it just me?
Is anyone hurt?
Spider-Man.
You saved my life.
Can you save God knows
how many lives by making sure
she didn't find what she
was looking for in there?
Before she passed out. she tried to say
something.
A name. Sarah.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her. she
managed to get in my mind for a moment.
Sarah was the name of someone I worked
closely with that recently passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of Sarah must have...
affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk to her when she
wakes up. if that's all right.
Of course.
She'll be transferred to our facility on
Roosevelt Island.
I'm just as eager to get
her talking as you are.
but let's not strain her
too much in one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
MJ!
It worked!
She's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this?
Did you want me to find it?
No.
Um. look. I can explain.
You need to take that off. please.
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this
conversation with Peter Parker.
He came to the party at our apartment the
other night.
And the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
Well. I've almost been
killed like five times in the
past 24 hours. so it's not
really working that well.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right?
So you just were gonna make that decision
for me?
I know.
I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to keep saying
that.
You're sorry.
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
I want you to tell me why you would do
this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be here if it wasn't for
me.
I didn't read you that
letter because I didn't
want anything like
that to happen to you.
But that's not really your decision to
make.
I know it's not. but you mean everything
to me.
And I've been trying to live my life
without you. but I...
I can't.
I love you.
This spell. or whatever it is that you
did...
It worked.
All these memories that you're saying that
we have together. I don't...
I don't have them.
And I do see why. you
know. she would love
you. the girl you wrote
that letter to. but...
I understand that you did what you had to
do to protect her.
And for that. I'm so grateful.
But I...
I don't love you.
Because I don't...
I don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
Really?
I'm sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone.
Um...
Do you mind taking me home?
Yeah. of course.
Thank you.
Yeah. sure.
Um... I'm gonna.
uh... Uh. yeah. yeah.
Yeah. of course.
Do you want to come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. maybe?
I would love that.
The Hulk. a.k.a.
Dr. Bruce Banner. is in custody. currently
being transferred to a psychiatric ward.
Oh. so sad.
After years as a peaceful academic.
the question the world asks today is.
what finally snapped?
Hey. I'm nearby.
MJ?
Yeah.
Uh... You're not gonna
believe this. but the Spidey
Tracker app says that
Spider-Man is in the direct vicinity.
Oh. yeah?
No way. that's crazy.
Uh. Ned?
Spider-Man?
Ned?
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
I'm not like a weirdo or anything.
He's a little weird.
Why. uh. why are you here?
Oh. I. uh... I was on
the subway platform.
I was on the platform. right. and she was
on her phone.
Yeah. I got a little distracted.
and the train was coming.
And I just swooped her right up.
Yeah. saved it. Ned.
Oh. my God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So. what if you're mid-swing. and you
decide you need to pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down the ground
level and run into a coffee
shop. and you're like. hey.
it's Spider-Man. I need to pee.
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a rooftop somewhere.
Ned.
Is this really what you want to be asking
him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
You can ask me anything.
You want to know how my web shooters work?
I mean. I already know how the web
shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously some sort of sheer
thinning fluid that is cycling within a
chamber. right. so it can keep its liquid
form.
And then when you activate it by pressing
all the triggers. it runs through a Teflon
turbine. and then it hardens when it
interacts with the air.
Right?
I mean. not exactly.
but... Okay. okay.
Well. then tell me what's in the web
fluid.
I would guess something like a long-chain
polymer.
Nylon?
That's pretty close.
Okay. okay.
What about Nomex or Okevlar?
All right. then.
Keep your secrets.
If you are very into the incident with the
dragon. I was barely involved.
All I did was simply give your uncle a
little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Ooh. bondme time.
You ordered bondmes?
I ordered five bondmes.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's gonna get fed.
Sorry about him.
He's just. like. very excited that you're
here.
Are you kidding?
It's. like. the most fun I've had in
years.
I really miss you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
Um...
When she was inhabiting you on the rooftop.
she kissed me. and I kissed her back.
Because I thought it was you. but I didn't
know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like I remember
anything anyway. so... Really?
Yeah.
It was weird.
It was. like. one second.
I was sitting at my desk. and the next
second I was lying on the street.
I don't know. like. a light switch went
off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. why?
Madsker said he remembered thinking about
someone named Sarah. but what you're
saying is that you don't remember anything
at all.
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you called Leshy.
Yeah. her name's Jean Grey.
I need some help determining the size of
some potatoes.
Potatoes?
I think that's back with Al.
I think Madsker lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Sarah?
Hmm. these potatoes sound meager.
Oh. well. that really is your office.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records.
and a lot of data related
to Jean Grey has been
scrubbed by damage control.
Data about what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister?
Hmm. Sarah Grey.
Also. a telepath.
Damage control took her into custody for
study and observation.
Wow.
I mean. you can probably guess what they
mean by that.
Experimentation and other human rights
violations?
Yes. exactly.
Wait. who are you?
Hi. Ned Leeds. big fan.
Hi!
Oh. I'm sorry.
I... I'm just so happy that
this sad man has friends.
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye.
She was just looking for her sister. and
I handed her to the people that took her.
I gotta go.
Okay. Peter?
Yeah.
Just be careful. all right?
Yeah. I will.
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her.
Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna have to hop.
Hop?
First. pick someone close.
And then...
You chop has a limit. but you can string
them together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go...
You're right back where you started.
Could you do that to everyone in this park
at once?
Yeah. maybe one day.
If you get really good.
Now could she just... send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that. anyway.
She was.
Before we changed.
Yeah. well. if that's all it takes for you
to stop being a mom. then you're not a mom.
What would you do if you had daughters
like us?
I'd love them.
Especially the redhead ones.
Shut up.
We have each other.
You and me have ice cream?
One mint chip. one chocolate?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm sorry. Jean.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake.
Heart rate is 94 BPM.
Jean. that's not going to work anymore.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
Jean?
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay?
You're safe.
Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister. you've been blessed with
a power that has the potential to do
tremendous good in the world. or
tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands of a child
is an impossible burden.
But imagine if that power
was placed in the hands
of people who actually
know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're going to change the world.
Jean.
Hey!
Frank?
I know where you are. what you're doing.
Oh yeah. and how's that?
You got eyes everywhere. kid.
Look. Frank. damage control kidnapped
Jean's sister.
Jean was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental horse shit.
You see what she can do and what she's
capable of.
What. you're going to let her loose?
Is that what you're going to do?
I'll tell you right now. you do that.
I handle it my way.
Frank. please. you don't...
Frank!
Distance check.
40-foot clearance.
Locking down the room.
Locking down.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jean. your powers are now fully
operational.
As you can tell. we are beyond your jump
radius.
Tell me what V-Max is.
You're the second person to ask me about
that.
I... I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you telepathically
across all that distance.
We did register a huge spike in that
session.
Fascinated.
What does it mean. asshole?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
I work with Sarah centered on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power.
and identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a
telepathic brain during a jump.
then perhaps we could replicate those
pathways in the mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together over many months of
trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what V-Max is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
The process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa. that's a pretty serious look
there. dude.
Hey. whoa. what the hell. man?
Come on. I'm a friend of Damage Control.
What are you doing?
Huh.
It's gonna be like that.
You wanna go.
All right.
Just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Did you stretch. you big stretcher?
I mean. you should do in your line of
work.
What about you?
You guys stretch?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Watch your head.
Where is Jean Grey?
Let's jump 26.
Recordings look good.
Excuse me. sir.
We have an intruder.
You were right.
She's much stronger than a sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well. Jean.
Jean?
Jean. can you hear me?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are evolving.
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this
room.
The brain waves are somehow affecting the
objects around her.
Shut it down.
I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister saw was this
goddamn room!
Shut it down!
I can't. sir.
Move.
I can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hands that will wield this power
are mine.
What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sarah.
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here to save a helpless girl
from damage control. you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now. so do you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
Jean!
Jean. please!
Isn't it funny how your
friends from damage
control developed a
special weapon just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them any more than
they trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank.
You got a problem. kid?
You gotta hold everyone within a kilometer
of the island.
Wait. what?
Look. if you're gonna do something.
you better do it now.
I'm trying!
Shit!
My sister died in this room.
Surrounded by these men.
And her only crime was that she was
special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't get to live a normal
life.
We don't get to have friends.
Or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just be honest with
yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Jean. please.
This won't make it right.
Come on. you're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her felt like you'd
lost everything.
If you come any closer. he dies!
They all do!
You know this won't bring her back.
right. Jean?
Don't be so sure I can't get into your
mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last
tried.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
that I've got powers?
You know. this whole thing can get really
scary.
You know that?
That's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't even imagine right now.
I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really great about yourself.
But I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes you'll be really lonely.
And sometimes. because you're special.
people can do dark. monstrous things to you.
But. this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful.
And the people who love you. we love you.
Not because you're special. we love you
because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels like you're totally
alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that. no matter how powerful
you become.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would have loved her.
Just because we've lost someone.
it doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean. we can't.
Trust me. I've been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's
true. I have no one.
You have me?
You hurt?
Fine. fine.
Peter.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
No. no. no. no. no. Peter.
You've got to get out of here.
They'll be looking for you.
No. no. no. no. no.
Please just stay with me.
Come on. hold on. come on. please.
You're gonna be okay.
Just go.
Look at me.
Shocked today.
A Spider-Man arrived at Bellevue Hospital
with a bullet wound.
Seemingly at death's door.
The reclusive crime
fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical
experts work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved
New York so many times is
now in the hands of
its best and brightest.
And the people of New York hold their
breath.
Frank. where am I?
No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
Hey.
Where's my mask?
What about that?
I got your covered.
You're good.
Where's Jean?
Is she okay?
Yeah. she's okay.
She's okay.
Where is she?
I think maybe she just left.
She was using her magic voodoo shit to
keep you alive.
Yeah. she's all right.
I'm sorry.
Frank. it's just I'm really sorry for what
I did.
It's a lot of things. but it sure shit
ain't okay. all right?
I've seen real bravery. kid. my day.
But dad. that was something else.
You crying?
No.
You know.
you look the exact way I thought you
would.
You're a nice kid.
Never had a friend like that.
Aren't we friends now?
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
I'm crying.
What are you talking about?
Bullshit.
Oh. yeah.
They've been doing it all night.
They've been here since you walked in.
Let's take a look.
Yo. kid. when you came in. they had to cut
through the suit.
But when you're ready to split.
I got a plan.
Hey. it's Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
Yeah!
I've been thinking a lot about what you
said.
And you'd be happy to know that I've
decided I'm not.
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore.
Let me see. mate.
I mean. I've still got a little
pain in my back. but I could
probably get back out there
if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know. but come on. you gotta
give me something.
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. Metzger's still missing.
Your friend. Black Widow.
she's been helping us dig through
all the records Damage
Control tried to have scrubbed.
Had me dropped by her office the other
day?
And how was that?
Well. uh. my skin feels amazing.
Attention all units. we have a confirmed
bank robbery in progress.
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No. we can handle a robbery.
Just... try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to E.J.
Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.
Hi.
Uh. hey.
Hey.
Oh. oh. uh. flower guy. right?
From the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay. hello.
Peter.
Because. bitch. I'm friends.
This memory's at home.
Feels like life is more than love.
I lose again. please. I beg.
For my whole
career too. yeah.
New Spider-Man sighting.
Location. unknown.
Location. found.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm